{
    "id": "02a918bbd9b84aaeba7f4d7d70528905",
    "title": "Sentence Agreement Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Economics ............................. his favourite subject.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e705e1b098fb4f0e9bd5dd7b979470d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Measles ............................. highly contagious.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "585a32125d9247b0bcae58ea5d735a53"
        },
        {
            "question": "Diabetes ............................ in my family.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "run",
                "runs",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "97b974acc18f4195ba1ce67d42218f8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rabies .............................. incurable.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1648e9a5b908421ea739ed74a00fdb01"
        },
        {
            "question": "Aerobics ............................ good for health.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a1213ee05b104402bd7f64931d09e834"
        },
        {
            "question": "No news .............................. good news.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "609736aef69344278db1996620e9a1f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Gymnastics ........................... her hobby at school.",
            "description": "Some nouns look plural with -s but they take a singular verb. Examples are: physics, mathematics, economics, mumps, measles, diabetes, rabies, news, politics, ethics, athletics, gymnastics, aerobics.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e79fa752d19640a5b7ebd9e8692083e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "What .............................. pliers used for?",
            "description": "Use a plural verb with jeans, trousers, pants, scissors, pliers etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8ce51a1a272447138cb5b349c093ea2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "My family ............................. lived in this house for twenty years.",
            "description": "Family can be followed by either a singular or a plural verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "40a9051c4d1043e2b9099a33bccfd5c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police ................................. searching for a bald guy in his forties.",
            "description": "Use a plural verb with police.",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ddfa0018f834482b28c853fd931dfb4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where ......................... my jeans?",
            "description": "Use a plural verb with jeans, trousers, pants, scissors, pliers etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1256e6a64dd74d27873fbb75dc1f843c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The staff .............................. not happy with the decision of the management.",
            "description": "Staff is usually followed by a plural verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94e649e3920a40d48f79dfa4fe8e6b50"
        }
    ]
}